<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-02-28T14:35:37-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Eduardo’s Blog</title><subtitle>This site is meant to show whatever I feel up to post, that can go from my academic projects to some of my drawings, pictures or videos that I like. Hope you enjoy your visit.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">My recent discovers on drawing</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/02/19/My-recent-discovers-on-drawing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My recent discovers on drawing" /><published>2018-02-19T22:33:10-05:00</published><updated>2018-02-19T22:33:10-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/02/19/My-recent-discovers-on-drawing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/02/19/My-recent-discovers-on-drawing.html">&lt;h4 id=&quot;hello-there-recently-ive-been-feeling-really-motivated-to-draw-and-to-improve-my-drawings-so-this-is-a-little-approach-to-that-area-of-my-life-in-particular&quot;&gt;Hello there, recently I’ve been feeling really motivated to draw, and to improve my drawings, so this is a little approach to that area of my life in particular.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Past year was quite the experience, I did a lot of stuff that I didn’t even thought about before, and because of that I kinda left behind drawing. Even though it was worth it, I wanted to get back into this activity that I enjoyed so much, and I knew that it was gonna take an essential role in my future, because a while back I noticed that Systems Engineering by it’s own wasn’t gonna cut it for me, I need that artistic/graphic/creative element in my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./../../../../../Zaraki draw.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;zaraki&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I started doing some really elaborated drawings in a rush to see incredible results asap, but I was copying other people’s work (mainly mangas) and drawing from reference too much, the creative side of drawing wasn’t even taken into account. I realized about it and started creating my own stuff, which was really odd at the beginning but my creativity is being put to work and that’s what matters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./../../../../../First Work.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Dream&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello there, recently I’ve been feeling really motivated to draw, and to improve my drawings, so this is a little approach to that area of my life in particular.</summary></entry></feed>